[
    {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Protocol for secure communication",
    "answer": "HTTPS"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "Default port number for HTTP",
    "answer": "80"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Default port number for HTTPS",
    "answer": "443"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Data structure used in BFS traversal",
    "answer": "Queue"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "Data structure used in DFS traversal",
    "answer": "Stack"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "Algorithm used for shortest path in graphs",
    "answer": "Dijkstra"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "Sorting algorithm with O(n log n) average complexity",
    "answer": "Merge Sort"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "Sorting algorithm that selects smallest element each pass",
    "answer": "Selection Sort"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Sorting algorithm based on swapping adjacent elements",
    "answer": "Bubble Sort"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Data structure with priority-based deletion",
    "answer": "Priority Queue"
  }
]